rdxsports.com 2016-12-26

# Privacy Policy

RDX values the bond it has with its valuable customers and completely understands the nature of sensitive information. Your particulars will always remain safe with us, and any such proceeding that involves you will be taken with your consent, and never without. We appreciate your trust, and aim to always uphold and build on it. 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RDX Sports uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.rdxsports.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by RDX Sports. 

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to: when Users visit our site, register on the site place, fill out an order form, subscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information. 

**Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously**

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information. 

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "Cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information and/or help user retrieve their shopping cart at any time. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or on alert when the cookies are being sent. If they do so, they may not be able to access some parts of the website or the entire website. 

**How we use collected information**

RDX Sports collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

**To improve customer service**

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

**To personalize user experience**

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 

**To improve our Site**

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

**To process transactions**

We may use the information Users provide about them when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 

**Using info for sending offers**

Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of RDX Sports customers. If you do not want to receive such offers, please adjust your account newsletter preference as that is how we will send out our promotions. 

**Sharing info for legal purposes**

We are entitled to use your info for legal purposes including police requests for any criminal or suspected illegal activity investigations in the capacity of responsible citizens. 

**To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature**

To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 

**To send periodic emails**

The email, Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. 

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

**We DO NOT save the credit card Information**

We DO NOT save credit card information of our customers. We only store the address and personal information but do not save Credit Card Information. 

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over an EV-SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**

RDX Sports has the authority to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page, send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and keep yourselves updated of the modifications. 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to the Administrative Head: 

RDX Inc. Limited   
Unit B3, Fernhill Mill   
Hornby St, Bury   
BL9 5BL
